https://www.cua.com.au/privacy-policy

Privacy and Open Banking | CUA
Important:
Please enable JavaScript in order to use this site.
Register for Online Banking
Login to...
Show debt who’s boss with a CUA Credit Card
0% balance transfers for 20 months and $0 balance transfer fee* T&Cs apply.
Earn 1.45 p.a* on your savings.
Simply deposit $1,000+ from a non-CUA account into your CUA transaction account. *T&Cs apply
Our Everyday Snap Account
Looking for a world of features and benefits with your everyday banking? Check out our Everyday Snap Account with $0 monthly account fees today.
Consolidate my debts
What will my repayments be?
Tools & Calculators
How much can I borrow?
What will my repayments be?
Which home loan is best for me?
What is a credit report?
Get there sooner
Secured Fixed Car Loan
6.79%p.a.
Life Insurance
Zurich Life Insurance, protect the financial futures of the ones you love with Zurich Life Insurance.
CUA Health Insurance
Get 2%-10% discount on your hospital cover if you're between 18-29 years old.
Insure with CUA and enjoy a $250 reward with every eligible policy*
Find out more
*T&Cs apply.
Send and receive money from overseas
$0 fee online international transfers and competitive rates on foreign currency
Search CUA
Login to...
Online banking
CUA Health Online
More
Banking on your mobile?
There's an app for that!
Download our CUA Mobile Banking App today.
It’s an optimised banking experience for your mobile, that’s secure, easy and convenient.
Download now.
Continue in browser
Search CUA
Search CUA
Login to...
Show debt who’s boss with a CUA Credit Card
0% balance transfers for 20 months and $0 balance transfer fee* T&Cs apply.
Earn 1.45 p.a* on your savings.
Simply deposit $1,000+ from a non-CUA account into your CUA transaction account. *T&Cs apply
Consolidate my debts
What are my repayments?
Tools & Calculators
Expand Tools & Calculators
How much can I borrow?
What will my repayments be?
Which home loan is best for me?
Get there sooner
Secured Fixed Car Loan
6.79%p.a.
Life Insurance
Zurich Life Insurance, protect the financial futures of the ones you love with Zurich Life Insurance.
CUA Health Insurance
Get 2%-10% discount on your hospital cover if you're between 18-29 years old.
Privacy at CUA
Credit Union Australia Limited, CUA Management Pty Ltd, CUA Health Pty Ltd and Credicorp Insurance Pty Ltd (the CUA Group, we or us) respects the privacy of our members' personal information. Our CUA Group Privacy Policy ("privacy policy") sets out important information including:
how we handle your personal information, including your credit-related information;
how you can request access to and correction of your personal information; and
what you can do if you think that we have breached your privacy
The CUA Group may collect personal information about you (including credit information and credit eligibility information). Credit reporting bodies are allowed under the Privacy Act 1988 and the Privacy (Credit Reporting) Code to handle such information. If you make a loan application or apply for loan repayment insurance, we may disclose your personal information to, or collect personal information about you from, a credit reporting body.
This information is used for the purpose of determining your eligibility for credit, and we may process the information to create an unsuitability assessment or other ratings of your suitability for credit.
If you fail to meet your payment obligations in relation to consumer credit or commit a serious credit infringement, CUA may be entitled to disclose this to the relevant credit reporting body.
You have the right to request credit reporting bodies not to use your credit reporting information for the purposes of pre-screening of direct marketing by us.
You have the right to request the credit reporting body not to use or disclose credit reporting information about you, if you reasonably believe that you have been, or are likely to be, a victim of fraud.
The Credit Reporting Bodies we exchange information with are:
Equifax
Ph: 13 83 32
www.equifax.com.au
Experian
Ph: 1300 783 684
www.experian.com.au
Illion
Ph: 13 23 33
www.illion.com.au
You may obtain a copy of any of the privacy policies of the above credit reporting bodies at the above websites or by contacting them using the details provided.
If you have any queries regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
Privacy Dispute Officer
Email: privacydisputes@cua.com.au
GPO Box 100, Brisbane QLD 4001
The Consumer Data Right and Open Banking
Banking institutions collect and hold information about you to meet our legal obligations and to develop new products and services.
How we collect and manage information is regulated by the Privacy Act and you can find more information in our privacy policy above.
The Consumer Data Right (CDR) is a government initiative that aims to give you more control over this information.
It is being rolled out in the banking sector and will move to other industries such as utilities in the near future.
In banking CDR is often referred to as "Open Banking".
Our CDR Policy, available here, contains more information on the Consumer Data Right, including how to access or correct your information, how to make a complaint and how we manage complaints.
Disclaimer
The information appearing on this site is for general information only and does not constitute an offer or an intention to enter into a legally binding contract. The products and services described in this site are only available to approved applicants who are Australian residents. All information regarding Credit Union Australia Limited (CUA) products can be withdrawn or changed without notice. Whilst every care has been taken in producing the information on this site, CUA does not guarantee the accuracy of the information. Subject to any terms implied by law and which cannot be excluded, CUA is not responsible for any loss, damage, cost or expense incurred by you as a result of any error, omission or misrepresentation in relation to this site.
Search CUA
Collection
Contact us
Call 133 282
Find a branch, ATM or Mobile Banker
CUA's Facebook
CUA's Twitter
CUA's YouTube
Need help achieving your goal?
